brandeps.com 2019-02-26

# Privacy policy | BrandEPS

* * *

### The privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

###  Any information received by BrandEPS through contact form, problem reporting form, feedback form, subscription form or through the email addresses contact@brandeps.com will only be used with the intention of answering the questions, suggestions or complaints sent by the users of the website. Any collected information will be kept confidential. 

### LOG FILE INFORMATION

###  Log file information is automatically reported by your browser or mobile application each time you access our website. For example, when you access our website, our server automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and other such information. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

### COOKIES

###  A cookie is a piece of information or file that is placed on the Users' device when they visit a website with the purpose of storing and recovering information about their use of the website. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons, which will send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP and the browser type you used. BrandEPS has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
